LINDSEY EDWARDS

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

Enthusiastic full stack developer who thrives in a fast-paced environment. Effective in utilizing problem solving skills to conquer any problems that arise. Team player that has worked on projects successfully, yet also self-motivated to work alone. Dedicated to advancing my skills through continued education and strives to stay active with the most current technologies and data trends.

CORE SKILLS

Java • Spring • Hibernate • JPA •
JavaScript • MVC• TDD • Agile (Scrum) •
Object Oriented Programming • AJAX •
JSON • Restful APIs • Responsive
Design / Mobile • SQL • Relational
Databases • Source Control / Git •
HTML5 • CSS3 • Flexbox • Grid

PROJECTS

Vi-Curiously:

Java | OOP | TDD | Scrum | Agile | Git| HTML 5 | CSS Team project that created a user review site to review some of lifes day to day activities.

High Street Hospital:

Java | OOP | TDD | Scrum | Agile | Git Solo project that organizes hospital staff and patients.

Virtual Pet:

Java | OOP | TDD | Scrum | Agile | Git Team developed console application that allows users to interact with a virtual pet.

CONTACT INFORMATION

614-668-4496 Columbus, OH Ledwards614@gmail.com

GitHub: @github.com/ledwards614

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/lindsey--edwards

EDUCATION

WE CAN CODE IT

Software Developer Apprentice | Jan 2019 to present

Attended top rated coding boot camp that taught the fundamentals of full stack development. Operated in a professional environment that encouraged team collaboration as well as personal development. Utilized agile development to build applications from the ground up implementing planning, design, and development of professional applications. The course successfully provided a thorough education to obtain software development certification.

FRANKLIN UNIVERSITY Undergrad | 2015

Coursework focused on Object-Oriented Programming, Algorithms and Data Structures, and Test Driven Development. Obtained skills necessary to think like a developer.

EMPLOYMENT

ADVANCED PHARMACY TECHNICIAN

Giant Eagle Pharmacy | Feb 2013 - Present

- Data entry of highly sensitive information detailing medical information of customers
- Responsible for third party billing to solve insurance billing problems.
- Communication with medical offices, other pharmacies, and patients through phone, fax, and e-mail.

PHARMACY TECHNICAN

BioScrip Pharmacy | June 2008- March 2012

- Provides exceptional customer service to customers, doctor's offices and insurance companies
- Worked in high volume mail order pharmacy communicating with doctor's to obtain refills for patients.

CREDIT UNION TELLER

Hawaiian Tel Federal Credit Union Oct 2006- Jan 2008

- Face to face client communication working with their confidential finances.
- Utilized organization and attention to detail to complete deposits, withdraws, money orders, and bank wires..